[
  {
    "front": "정원",
    "back": "Garden"
  },
  {
    "front": "심다/식물",
    "back": "Plant"
  },
  {
    "front": "씨앗",
    "back": "Seed"
  },
  {
    "front": "새",
    "back": "Bird"
  },
  {
    "front": "먹다",
    "back": "Eat"
  },
  {
    "front": "화난",
    "back": "Cross"
  },
  {
    "front": "보다",
    "back": "Look"
  },
  {
    "front": "생각/아이디어",
    "back": "Idea"
  },
  {
    "front": "만들다",
    "back": "Make"
  },
  {
    "front": "허수아비",
    "back": "Scarecrow"
  },
  {
    "front": "돕다",
    "back": "Help"
  },
  {
    "front": "가방",
    "back": "Bag"
  },
  {
    "front": "그리다/칠하다",
    "back": "Paint"
  },
  {
    "front": "얼굴",
    "back": "Face"
  },
  {
    "front": "부르다/이름짓다",
    "back": "Call"
  },
  {
    "front": "살아있는",
    "back": "Alive"
  },
  {
    "front": "뛰다",
    "back": "Jump"
  },
  {
    "front": "공중/하늘",
    "back": "Air"
  },
  {
    "front": "손을 흔들다",
    "back": "Wave"
  },
  {
    "front": "어디",
    "back": "Where"
  },
  {
    "front": "가다",
    "back": "Go"
  },
  {
    "front": "밴드/악단",
    "back": "Band"
  },
  {
    "front": "시작하다",
    "back": "Begin"
  },
  {
    "front": "연주하다/놀다",
    "back": "Play"
  },
  {
    "front": "춤추다",
    "back": "Dance"
  },
  {
    "front": "갑자기",
    "back": "Suddenly"
  },
  {
    "front": "열쇠",
    "back": "Key"
  },
  {
    "front": "빛나다",
    "back": "Glow"
  },
  {
    "front": "시간",
    "back": "Time"
  },
  {
    "front": "집",
    "back": "Home"
  }
]